http://www.wkf.com/support/privacy-policy/

Local Delivery
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (www.wkf.com).  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Registration
In order to use this website, a user may complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.  Our website can also be used without registration, you can check out as a “guest”.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form.  To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).  This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
-          See what data we have about you, if any.
-          Change/correct any data we have about you.
-          Have us delete any data we have about you.
-          Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 314.352.7575 or contact us via the customer service selection on this web page (above).
×
Notice
General Store Information
Locations:
Walter Knoll Florist Downtown Saint Louis Store:
2765 LaSalle St
Saint Louis, MO 63104-1917
(314) 352.7575
Walter Knoll Florist Ladue:
9776 Clayton Rd
Ladue, MO 63124
(314) 994-7304
Walter Knoll Florist Arnold Greenhouse:
#2 Knoll Pl
Just off Hy21 west of 141
Arnold, MO 63010
636.296.4241
WKF Events & Weddings:
2765 Lasallle St
Saint Louis, MO 63104
(314) 633-8780
Harold's Wholesale Florist:
2755 LaSalle St
Saint Louis, MO 63104
(314) 352-2134
Walter Knoll Florist O'Fallon:
2516 Highway K
Ofallon, MO 63368
636-240-6699
Walter Knoll Florist South County:
9926 Kennerly Rd
(Across From Mercy South Hospital/ Near St Louis Bread)
Saint Louis (County), MO 63128-2704
(314) 633-8800
Walter Knoll Florist Garden Center & Greenhouse:
1010 California Ave
at LaSalle
Saint Louis, MO 63104
(314) 633-8775
Walter Knoll Florist Corporate Offices:
